ILGWU New York Dress Joint Board Minutes 5780/033
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Joint Board. Grievance Committee. Minutes., 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Book V
- Joint Board. Grievance Committee. Minutes., 1958-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Book VI
- Joint Board. Appeal Committee. Minutes., 1934-1942 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Joint Board. Appeal Committee. Minutes., 1943-1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Joint Board. Committee on Claims. Minutes., 1945-1949 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Vol. I
- Joint Board. Committee on Claims. Minutes., 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Vol. II
- Joint Board. Committee on Claims. Minutes. [folder 1 of 2], 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Joint Board. Committee on Claims. Minutes. [folder 2 of 2], 1952 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Minutes, Rules, Regulations & Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Minutes, Rules, Regulations & Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1944-1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Minutes, Rules, Regulations & Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Minutes, Rules, Regulations & Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Minutes, Rules, Regulations & Correspondence., 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Joint Board. Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Joint Board. Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Joint Board. Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Joint Board. Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Vol. III
- Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Vol. IV
- Health and Welfare Fund. [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Analyses of Remittances & Investigations., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Report on Financial Statements., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Retirement Fund. Financial Statements., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Health and Welfare Fund. Audit Procedure, Findings & Recommendations., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 1 of 2], 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 2 of 2], 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 1 of 3], 1956-1960 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 2 of 3], 1956-1960 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 3 of 3], 1956-1960 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Retirement Fund. Misc. Records. [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1965 (Box 7, Folder 21)